as a result of Putin’s war, the Slavs are dying Yes
в результате войны Путина гибнут славяне
yes yes So Putin’s war
Да да да Значит Путин Путинская война
is killing the Slavs Yes yes
убивает славян
yes that is the war that
Да да да то есть война которую развязал
Putin started is killing the Slavs
Путин убивает славян
yes yes And now the question for Ivan Putin
да да И теперь вопрос для Ивана Путин
is killing the
убивает
Slavs what kind of nonsense are you
славян ты что за чепуху
talking about
несёшь
Hello I wish you good health I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравия желаю я из города
Khmelnitsky
Хмельницке Вы
Where are you from?  Yes, it’s cool from
откуда Да с
Krasnodar,
Краснодара
that is, you are from Krasnodar, yes, yes,
прикольно то есть вы краснодарец да да
from what village are
да С какой станицы родом Ни с какой а то
you from? Not from any, that is, you are not from a Cossack family Yes, you are a
есть вы вы не с казацкого рода Да вы
newcomer, Emelya Yes,
приезжий Емеля
yes, yes, and where are your
Да да да име А откуда ваши
ancestors from
предки с
Ukraine? And what are you doing in Russia now? Well, so
Украины А что вы сейчас в России
not to offend Well, as if well,
делаете Ну дабы не обидеть Ну как бы ну
just
просто
living, living, or
живу живёте или
surviving, living, living, I
выживает живу живу
don’t
не
understand, you read this Tale about the Cossack
понял вы читали такую Сказ про казака
Golota, yes, but look, I’m interested
голоту да А вот смотрите мне интересно
More ska Tale about Ivan the Fool That’s
Больше ска Сказ про Ивана дурака Вот
why in Russian fairy tales Ivan the
российс почему в российских сказках Иван
Fool is not me, let’s not translate
дурак давайте вы не будете переводить не
it  answered with you said about the question I
я же ответил с вы сказали про вопрос я
said I know yes yes And now I’m
сказал знаю да да А теперь я вам
asking you it’s not a fairy tale but Duma Duma about the
спрашиваю там не сказка а Дума Дума про
Cossack Golota now
казака голота теперь
with everything Ivan
с все Иван
the Fool Well, because Ivan the Fool Well, why is
дурак Ну потому что Иван дурак Ну почему
there no character in Ukrainian fairy tales Ivan the Fool or Bogatyr cats
Иван дурак там либо Богатырь коты
peas  Kato everything And you Ivan is a
горошка Като всё А у вас Иван
fool, this
дурак это
goes how to say something e
идёт как сказать-то е Господи боже ты
My God, well, roughly speaking, that
мой ну грубо говоря что
willow mathematical solutions to solve and He will
ива математические решения решать а Он
take a club and then everything will happen
дубины возьмёт как и вот всё произойдёт
That is, I understand correctly that the main
То есть я правильно понимаю что главный
character of Russian fairy tales is the most
персонаж российских сказок самый
famous - This is Ivan  a fool and well, this is a
известный - Это Иван дурак и вот ну это
man with a certain physical strength
человек определённой физической силой
who affects everyone else
который воздействует на все остальные
nothing in this jealous frog
нифига вот в этой в ревно лягушка ничего
he had nothing there, in short, on the contrary,
у него там силы не было короче наоборот
he lost bullets somehow Two brothers
он пуль нул короче как-то Два брата
shot normally, but in short, he
нормально стрельнули да он короче
shot somewhere in the
стрельнул куда-то в
swamp  Well, that’s how it turned out, that is,
болото Ну вот так получилось то есть
Ivan Ivan is a fool, he’s just not strong, he’s
Иван Иван дурак он как раз не сильный он
just a
просто
fool, he’s outplayed the
дурак он за счёт своего ума Переиграл
whole situation at the expense of his mind, but he’s a
всю ситуаци поди как за счёт ума Но он
fool again if he’s outplayed at the expense of his mind,
дурак ещё раз если он за счёт ума
but they call him Ivan the fool, not
Переиграл но его называют Иван дурак не
Ivan a genius, for example.  and Ivan is a
Иван гений например а Иван
fool Well, it happened. How did it
дурак Ну так получилось А как так
happen that such a smart person
получилось что такого умного человека
who Outplayed everyone was called a fool
который всех Переиграл назвали дураком
at the expense of his intelligence Well,
за счёт ума Ну
how can I explain it to you so that you can
вот как бы тебе объяснить чтобы тебе
understand yes
понятно было да
yes Well,
да Ну
look at
смотри
the person who is a blockhead, let’s call him a
человек который дуболом назовём его так
blockhead, well, he’s purely Well, just physically
дуболом ну он чисто Ну просто физически
everyone
всех
destroys such a thought woke up in my head
уничтожает такой проснулась в голове
I can think about it he is
мысль я могу размышлять он
so
такой
thoughtful in front of you
размыслова перед тобой
grenade What will you do What does
граната Что ты сделаешь
Ivan the
Причём тут Иван
Fool have to do with it Let us fairy tales nene during
дурак Давай мы сказки нене во время
Ivan the Fool during fairy tales there was no
Ивана дурака во время в сказках не было
grenade gd5 there is
гранаты гд5 справа от тебя
a corpse on your right don't let's don't run away four
труп не давай давай не убегай четыре
soldiers wait  then Ivan the Fool is already
солдата подожди то то Иван дурак уже
Dead Yes, because he came to
Мёртвый Да потому что пришёл в
Ukraine
Украину
Yes, Ivan the Fool, come on, that corpse on the
Да Ивана Дура давай так тот труп который
right is Ivan the Fool, died, or let it
справа это Иван дурак умер или как
be Ivan the Fool, Ivan the Fool will be
пускай будет Иван дурак Иван дурак будет
willow, then look, if he came to
ива всё то смотри если он приехал в
another country from what is his mind  where he
другую страну из то в чём его ум где он
Outplayed if he now realized
Переиграл если он он вот теперь понял
that he is Ivan the fool, he came to a foreign
что он Иван дурак он приехал в чужую
country and there he is Ivan the fool on the right
страну и там он Иван дурак с правой
side four on the healthy side is
стороны четыре со здоровой стороны
correct then look, the one who
правильно то смотри то тот который
came from a foreign country from Russia to
приехал из чужой страны из России в
Ukraine to conquer something Heavenly you
Украину завоевать что-то Рае ты труп
move the corpse onto the grenade So wait, he’s already
подвинь на гранату Так подожди он уже
gone, that’s all, we understand that he is
дру вот всё так мы поняли что он потому
because look again, I don’t understand. What does it have to do with him
что ещё раз смотри я не понял При чём
if he’s a fool, if you say that he’s
тут если он дура если ты говоришь что он
smart, smart Yes, but he’s a fool, I now understand that
умный умный Да но дурак я теперь понял
he’s smart, I’d think that he’s everyone  He outplayed
он умный бы думал что он всех Переиграл
Yes, he went to Ukraine and that’s why he’s Ivan a
Да поехал в Украину и поэтому он Иван
fool, yes You must be smart because
дурак да Умный должен быть ты потому что
move a corpse onto a grenade and you’ll save
труп подвинь на гранату и ты спасёшь
lives. Look like that again, let’s
жизни ещ раз так смотри давай ещ раз
look again,
смотри
okay, let’s look again. So,
давай хорошо давай ещё раз смотри Значит
there’s a grenade, we don’t know there, like it’s
есть граната мы не знаем там типа она
not activated  activated there is a corpse
активирована не активирована есть труп
but we know that the corpse is Ivan is a fool
но мы знаем что труп - Это Иван дурак
yes yes yes so look now I understand
да да да так смотри теперь я понял
why he is a fool because he came from
почему он дурак потому что он приехал из
another country like How to capture
другой страны вроде Как захватить
Ukraine which Lenin invented Yes but
Украину которую придумал Ленин Да но
Lenin was not a fool he invented Ukraine and
Ленин был не дурак он придумал Украину а
this Ivan decided  take over Ukraine and he's
этот Иван решил захватить Украину и он
already lying dead, that's why he's Ivan a
лежит уже Мёртвый то вот почему он Иван
fool,
дурак
so no And why Well, why is he exactly
так нет А почему Ну почему он именно вот
why the one who came from Russia to
почему тот кто приехал из России
take over Ukraine is lying dead, why is he
захватить Украину лежит труп почему он
Ivan a
Иван
fool, I asked another question So
дурак я другой вопрос задавал Так
wait, let's figure it out now You've
подожди давай Сейчас разберёмся Ты меня
confused me why here  He’s Ivan,
запутал почему вот он именно Иван дурак
your fool, he’s lying. I’m asking, What will you do?
твый лежит Я спрашиваю Что ты сделаешь
You have Ira, that’s why it
Вот у тебя есть Ира это за сди это
depends. Well, why is he Ivan the fool? I’m here, let
зависит Ну почему он Иван дурак я вот
’s sort it out now, let’s
давай сейчас мы разберёмся давай с
sort it out with Ivan the fool. Well, this is important.
Иваном дураком разберёмся Ну это важно
We started with Ivan the fool. Yes, from
Мы же начали с Ивана дурака канву Да из
fairy tales  And now they have transferred it to reality.
сказок А теперь перенесли в реальность
That is, I see this is not just a fairy-tale
То есть я смотрю Это не просто сказочный
character, this is real. That is, he had
персонаж это реальный То есть у него был
some kind of prototype that was embodied.
прототип какой-то который воплотился
Ivan in the fairy tale, Ivan is a fool, he is because he
Иван сказке Иван дурак он он потому что
gave his life for the wrong
отдал свою жизнь не за
thing, that is, he And understood, that is, fi in  the fact
то то есть он А понял то есть фи в том
that he gave his life for Putin,
что он отдал свою жизнь за Путина
that’s why he’s Ivan a
поэтому он Иван
fool, I didn’t say that, I said it
дурак я этого не говорил Я это сказал
correctly, I said it, well, you said it,
правильно я это сказал ну ты это сказал
yes, I understand, I liked your
да да Всё понял ну мне понравилась твоя
idea, Ivan cancer gave his life for Putin, for
э идея Иван рак отдал жизнь за Путина за
a vacuum cleaner, I don’t know there.  in general, for
пылесос там я не знаю Мне вообще за
Putin and for the toilet, look, that is, let’s do it like this.
Путина и за унитаз да смотри то есть
Ivan the fool is the one who gave
давай так Иван дурак это тот кто отдал
his life for Putin and for the toilet, yes.
свою жизнь за Путина и за унитаз да
Well, I said for the vacuum cleaner. Well, if you want for the
Ну я сказал за пылесос Ну хоче за
vacuum cleaner, let’s do it, just give the vacuum cleaner.
пылесос давай так давай пылесос вот
Who gave it, it turns out that Ivan
просто Кто отдал получается что Иван
the fool is the one  who gave his life for
дурак - это тот кто отдал жизнь за
Putin, no no, well, you just
Путина так нет нет ну ты же только что
said that Ivan is a fool, he gave his life for
сказал вот Иван дурак он отдал жизнь за
Putin, let’s say this Ivan a fool gave
Путина допустим этот Иван дурак отдал
Zai
Зай
question Who gave his life for Putin, that Ivan is a fool No, it’s
вопро Кто отдал жизнь за Путина тот Иван
not true, that is, not everyone who
дурак Нет неправда то есть не все кто
gave their life for Putin Ivan is a fool  yes,
отдали жизнь за Путина Иваны дураки да
yes, although you know, I’ll tell you this The one who
да хотя знаешь я тебе так скажу Тот кто
gave his life for Putin and
отдал жизнь за Путина и
anyone you see We are Russian folk tales,
любой видишь Мы русские народные сказки
they lead to the correct to the
они приводят к правильным к
correct conclusions, and the one who gave for the
правильным выводам а тот кто отдал за
Slavic people
славянский народ
would be
бы
those Yes, sometimes So Well,
те Да пором Так
I can’t do this, I can’t but  I
Ну я этого не могу сделать не могу а я
correctly understood what kind of Slavic
правильно понял что ты за Славянский
dorot you are, you are
дорот ты
a Slav, yes, you can name some Slavic
славянин да да можешь назвать славянских
Gods,
Богов
but why should I name them if
каких-то а зачем мне их называть если
they are already present? Well, what
они и так присутствует Ну каких ты
Slavic gods do you know that our ancestors honored,
славянских богов которых чтили наши
you know, I’ll repeat it again, you thought the tale about the Cossack
ты я ещё раз повторю ты Сказ про казака
Golota  wait, let's figure it out now with
голоту считал подожди давай мы сейчас с
Ivan the fool and the Slavic gods,
Иваном дураком и славянскими богами
look Ivara Come on Ivan the fool who
смотри Ивара Давай Иван дурак который
was in fairy tales,
был в сказках
yes,
да
I remember Ukraine Look No, well, you
помнишь я Украине Смотри Не ну ты сейчас
live in Russia now You're a genetic Ukrainian,
живёшь в России Ты генетический украинец
but in reality you're already Ivan, you've already grown up in
но реально ты уже Иван ты уже вырос в
Russia
России
and Ivan It's no one by chance  there in Ukraine they
а Иван Это случайно никого там в Украине
don’t call Ivan not that Ivan And you Ivan
не называют Иван не не то Иван А вы Иван
understand that these are different Ivans, we have Ivan
понимаешь это разные Иваны у нас Иван
without us Ivan Ivan there And you have Ivan with the
без у нас Иван Иван там А у вас Иван с
prefix which is for Putin, that’s your
приставкой который за Путина вот тебя
name What is your name Ivan for Putin
как зовут Как тебя зовут Иван за Путина
not What is
не Тебя как
your name Ivan  Putin And I understand your name is
зовут Иван Путина А понял у тебя имя
Ivan, the surname is Putin, you are female Ivan, I
Иван фамилия Путина ты женской Иван
understand this is the Chechen name Ivan, but for
понял это чеченское имя Иван но за
Putin, too. That is, you are called
Путина тоже То есть вы вас зовут
Ivan, Ivan is my name, but Putin. Well, there is
Иван Иван за меня зовут а пута Ну там
Ivan, and so look, and Putin is a surname from the
Иван а так смотри а Путин фамилия от
word, so I understand that someone  from his
слова так понимаю что кто-то из его
ancestors was
предков был
Yes, I don’t know, I understood But look, Putin Is he for the
Да не в курсе понял А смотри Путин Он за
Slavic people or against the Slavic
славянский народ или против Славянского
people
народа
Well, for the hierarchy Well, let’s put it this way, Putin, uh,
Ну за иерархия Ну путь давай так Путин
do it so that there are more Slavs
ээ делать так чтобы славян было больше
or there are
или
no Slavs, so that there are more
славян нет чтобы было больше так во
Slavs during Putin’s war against Ukraine
время войны Путина против Украины славян
more or
стало больше или
less less less that means Putin
меньше меньше меньше то значит Путин
is doing so that there are fewer Slavs
делает так чтобы славян ставало меньше
so Well, he is more for that is, Putin is Slavs
так Ну он больше за то есть Путин славян
So well, not Slavs Ukrainians Well, Ukrainians
Так ну не славян украинцев Ну украинцы -
are Slavs and Russian Slavs are dying in this
это славяне и Русские славяне на это
war, both Russians and Ukrainians
войне гибнут и русские и украинцы
who are Slavs are true How can you not  you can
которые славяне верно Как ты не можешь
recognize My people and the Tale about Kaza
признать Мой народ и Сказ про каза
Golota also I can’t recognize Ukraine
голоту также я не могу признать Украину
Look, I understand correctly that uh, as a
Смотри я правильно понимаю что ээ в
result of Putin’s war, the Slavs are Russians
результате войны Путина славяне русские
and Ukrainians
и украинцы
yes Absolutely true Absolutely true that
да Абсолютно верно Абсолютно верно то
is, Putin is Slavic
есть Путин
No, let’s do it that way, as a result of
славян Нет давай так в результате войны
Putin’s war the Slavs Yes
Путина славяне
yes yes So  Putin Putin's war of the
Да да да Значит Путин Путинская война
Slavs
славян
Yes yes yes that is the war that
Да да да то есть война которую развязал
Putin unleashed of the Slavs
Путин славян
yes yes And now the question is for the
да да И теперь вопрос для пу
Slavs What kind of nonsense are you talking about
славян Ты что за чепуху
Yes he understood the Slavs Putin the Slavs
несёшь Да он славян понял Путин славян
everything That's what I wanted to understand so look
всё Вот это я хотел и понять так смотри
now at the question If Putin Yes look if
теперь вопрос Если Путин Да смотри если
Putin  the Slavs, the Slavs are becoming fewer and
Путин славян то славян стаёт меньше и
fewer Yes, Putin means they are committing genocide of the
меньше Да Путин значит делат геноцид
Slavs, we need to stop
славян нам нужно остановить
Putin no. Why continue the Slavs,
Путина нет А зачем продолжит славян
he will continue the Slavs of Ukrainian
он продолжит славян украинского
origin and Russian, too, the Russians are
происхождения и русского тоже русские
dying too, and the Russian Ukrainians are dying, you
гибнут тоже и русские украинцы гибнут
know, both of them are Slavs. We are one
понимаешь И те и те славяне Мы ж один
people, you know, one people  we from Kievan
народ понимаешь один народ мы с Киевской
Rus went one people who we went
Руси пошли один народ которые мы пошли
this is a sacrifice for which we went And I understand that
это жертва на которые мы пошли А понял
you are sacrificing Russians
то есть вы русских приносите в
Absolutely right So stop That is,
жертву Абсолютно верно Так стоп То есть
this is a
это
sacrifice this is a sacrifice yes yes That is, you understand
жертва это жертва да да То есть вы понял
that is, you are not Christians you are pagans
то есть вы не христиане вы язычники
sacrificing there  some people Yes, yours,
приносите там людей каких-то Да своих
you said this is a
ты ты сказал это
sacrifice, so yes, we bring the Slavs,
жертва так да мы приносим славян всё то
look, if you bring the Slavs, then
смотри если вы приносите славян значит
you are making an offering. You know
вы делаете приношение Ты знаешь что
what golota is. Wait, then
такое голота Подожди то
you are naked. I’m asking you, you know,
ты голо Я тебя спрашиваю ты знаешь
answered to Ivan Look, this is you be you  you
ответил на во Иван Смотри это ты бе ты
are making an offering You understand the
делаешь приношение Ты понимаешь
offering You are doing
приношение ты делаешь
this Yes they cannot bring the Slavs The one who
это да не могут приносить славян тот кто
brings the
приносит
Slavs Okay
славян Хорошо
I will come for you No what you see but you
я я приду за тобой нет то что ты вижу но
will come You are at most shorter in
придёшь Ты максимум короче в
your Well, it’s okay at
свой Ну ничего страшного хотя
least what you ran away from You can answer
бы а что ты убежал ты можешь ответить на
my questions  I just can’t look,
мои вопросы меня просто не могу смотри
there’s interest, I can’t Look, they’re
интерес есть я не могу Смотри
eliminating who doesn’t answer them yes yes
устраняются кто на них не отвечает да да
yes answer Show your face you know who the
да ответь Покажи лицо ты знаеш кто такое
Cossack Golota is face Show the Kaza you’re already
казак голота лицо Покажи каза ты уже
sick of that Cossack at Golota I’ll
задолбал с тем казаком у голота я тебе
just
вот
wait for you, calm down Come on we’re not up to it
подожди успокойся Давай мы мы не до
we've dealt with Ivan the
разобрались с Иваном
fool, let's talk
дураком поговорим
about I'm only answering your question
про Я только отвечаю на твои вопрос Ты
You didn't answer to the end You didn't answer to the end, you
не ответил до конца Ты до конца не
know, let's
ответил понимаешь да
go look at the question where I'm not answering my questions
пошл смотри вопрос гда на мои вопросы не
I'm just answering
отвеча Я только отвечаю
my questions, you know, I'll
мне вопросы понимаешь
explain about Ivan, let's look, calm
объясню про Ивана давай смотри успокойся
down Let's finish about Ivan  fool and
Давай мы закончим про Ивана дурака и
I’ll answer your question look Tell me
отвечу на твой вопрос смотри Назови мне
in which fairy tales Ivan the
в каких сказках встречался Иван
Fool met in many of you all Yes for example At
дурак во многих тебе все Да например
least
Хотя бы
three on the stove he was lying on the stove Emelya was lying
три на печи он лежал на печи Емеля лежал
no on the stove was lying
нет на печи лежал
Emelya this was different yes and Ivan the Fool in
Емеля это друго был да а Иван дурак в
which fairy tale Which fairy tale where  he
какой сказке Какая сказка где он
was lying Well, the name is the name of the fairy tale Why am
лежал Ну назва название сказки Почему
I just interested, well for the sake of interest, well,
мне просто интересно ну ради интереса ну
no more no less, why the answer to your
ни больше ни меньше почему на твои
questions is because you didn’t follow up Here,
вопросы так потому что ты не довел Вот
answer three fairy tales Three fairy tales in which
ответь три сказки Три сказки в которых
Ivan was a fool Here is the one who
был Иван дурак Вот тот который с жабой
kissed the toad as the fairy tale
целовался как сказка
was called
называлась
Ivan no
Иван нет
and the fairy tale What
а сказка Как
was the name of Ivan Tsarevich changes profession
называлась Иван царевич меняет профессию
no no What was the name of the fairy tale The Great
не не Как называлась сказка Великая
Russian fairy tale about Ivan the Fool where He
Русская сказка про Ивана дурака где Он
kissed a toad and thought
жабу целовал и думал что
it was a jealous frog Oh so the second
это ревна лягушка О так вторая
fairy tale the
сказка
second
вторую
three ska
три ска
about Let's stress you have two
про Давай напряги тебе осталось две
fairy tales left one fairy tale with Ivan the drum is always
сказки одна сказка с Иваном друм всегда
with  in the fairy tale there were three brothers three fairy tales need to be
у сказке было три брата три сказки надо
named jealous frog
назвать ревна лягушка ещё
two more Well, give me some hints, don’t you want
две Ну давай подсказки не ты хочешь
me to listen about golota and answer,
чтобы я выслушал про голоту и ответил
give me two fairy tales, there are still two left I didn’t
давай две сказки ещё осталось две Я не
intend for you to be taller I want to
собирался чтоб ты выша голо Я хочу
answer yes, I’ll answer you Yes Tell me
ответить да я те отвечу Да Назови мне е
two  those fairy tales I promise I will answer your
две сказки те обещаю я отвечу на твой
question about
вопрос по
the lot And if you can’t answer you know
лоте А если не сможешь ответить знаешь
how in a fairy tale like the wizard says and
как в сказке типа волшебник говорит а
if you can’t Good fellow answer
коль не сможешь Добрый молодец ответить
me fairy tales Three in which Ivan was a fool then
мне сказки Три в которых Иван дурак был
I’ll switch you over and you won’t know
то переключу тебя я и не узнаешь ты
The truth about golota and not  there will be no peace in your
Правды про голоту и не будет ни в твоей
soul and you will wander like that
душе покоя и будешь ты скитаться как тот
Ivan through the swamps looking for his toad and you won’t
Иван по болотам искать свою жабу и не
find it and the toad will eat you from the middle because
найдёшь и жаба съест тебя с середины ибо
Ivan you are in essence and not in
Иван ты есть по сути а не по
name
имени
understood
понял
Yes, I understand, let’s say two more
Да всё ж понял давай ещё две
fairy tales, fairy tales Let’s say two  fairy tales with
сказки сказки Давай сказал две сказки с
Ivan the Fool on Google he's on the phone
Иваном дураком на Гугле он в телефоне
Look for Emelya not Emelya it's him Emelya was this
Ищи Емеля не Емеля это он Емеля был это
fairy tale and pikes there I don't know what it
сказка и щуки там я не знаю как она
was called But it's yes I'll Google it
называлась Но это да загуглю давай Гугли
let's Google Let's
Давай
Google So Ivan met Google
Гугли Итак Иван познакомился с Гуглом
tundun
тундун
dun hung
дун завис
no no no
не
Hang on he  pocha Google this and
Зависай поду он поча Гугла это и
hung Ivan the fool e o razvi su super
завис Иван дурак е о разви су супер
super what other fairy tales would hang
супер то ещё какие сказки бы зависало
daka con hump Sivka Burka so little
дака кон горб Сивка бурка так конёк
hunchbacked horse and Sivka Burka counted so well
горбунёк и Сивка бурка так хорошо
let me give you permission to ask
засчитали давай я тебе разрешаю спросить
me about
меня про
golota Well, tell me about the fairy tale about the
голоту Ну расскажи мне про сказку про
Cossack golota I  I don’t know, I don’t remember this, it’s
казака голоту Я не знаю не помню эту это
not a fairy tale, but there was a Duma about the Cossack famine,
не сказка а Дума про казака голод была
but I don’t
но я её не
remember it, and everything and
помню и всё и
everything you get for me is not what I said, that
всё ты получается мне не я сказал что
I will answer your question. You
что я отвечу тебе на твой вопрос Ты мне
asked me a question, I answered it, I answered it
задал вопрос я на него ответил ответил
honestly.  I don’t
по-честному Я её не
remember it I answered seven of your questions and
помню я ответил на семь твоих вопросов а
you answered me I just didn’t understand, well, I
ты мне ответил просто я не понял ну я
really didn’t understand I answered honestly I
реально не понял Я честно ответил Я тебе
told you that I would answer your question you
сказал что я отвечу на твой вопрос ты
asked it and I answered I kept my
его задал и я ответил Я задержал своё
word I answered as I am  I don’t remember
слово я ответил так как есть я не помню
it, I even had a book about Duma about the
её у меня книжка даже была Дума про
Cossack Golo
казка голо
in childhood Well, I don’t remember Well, you
в детстве Ну я не помню Ну вот
see, they once thought What a
видишь когда-то думали Как выглядит
bummer it looks like,
[__] это
dude You have a face like you
оно чувак У тебя такое лицо как будто ты
put it in, in short, you
в вложил короче
put it in And the next day Like it
вложил в А на следующий день Типа она
burst  You're
лопнула Ты
just really,
просто просто реально
I'm straining my whole soul here to
я тут всю ку свою напряг чтобы
remember No, you wanted to look, you
помнить Не ну ты хотел смотри у тебя
had a dream to have your
была мечта чтобы тебе ответили на твой
question answered, your dream came true, what else do you
вопрос твоя мечта сбылась что ты ещё
want by making the right requests to the
хочешь правильно став запросы во
Universe
Вселенную
So you don't run away You like it,
Так ты не убегаешь Тебе нравится
like it and I'm already  I took it and got scared,
нравится и прям я уже взял и испугался
look, I still have a voice
давай смотри у меня ещё есть голосовой
assistant, you actually have a voice assistant,
помо ты вообще у меня голосовой помощник
I’ll tell you now,
я сейчас
well, by the way, about the Cossack golota
ну можно кстати у и про казака голоту
In short, I’ll ask
Короче я спрошу
like this
так
now Well,
сейчас А
I have a voice assistant Ivanka,
ну у меня есть голосовой помощник Иванка
don’t don’t
не не
run away, don’t run away, don’t
убегай не убегай не
run away, everything Listen.  By the way, I have
убегай всё Слушай у меня есть кстати
Ivanka Think about Ivanka, but she’s not stupid
Иванка Прикинь Иванка но она не дура
Ivanka is not stupid Ivanka knows everything Ivanka
Иванка не дура Иванка всё знает Иванка
Tell me please Ivan the Fool - This is a
Скажи пожалуйста Иван дурак - Это
fairy-tale character from Russian fairy tales Ivan
сказочный персонаж русских сказок Иван
the Fool - This is not a fairy-tale character, but
дурак - Это не сказочный персонаж а
a real one in Russia, half of the population is
реальный в России половина населения
like this again Ivanka didn’t hear me, I
такие ещё раз Иванка мне не расслышала я
asked  Ivan the Fool - Is this a fairy-tale
попросил Иван дурак - Это сказочный
character from Russian fairy tales or not Iva the
персонаж русских сказок или нет ива
Fool - This is not a fairy-tale character but a
дурак - Это не сказочный персонаж а
real one in Russia half the population is
реальный в России половина населения
such an interesting
такие интересная
version Listen, I understand that you were
версия Слушай я я так понимаю что ты
very upset after Yes, my answer
очень расстроился после Да моего ответа
about the Cossack Golota
про казака голоту
yes yes not really well how are you-  then don’t be too
да да не совсем ну ты как-то сильно не
upset don’t go near the windows,
расстраивайся не подходи к окнам
for example, today it’s good
например сегодня хорошо
Yes, you know, there are no snipers there Yes, no
Да знаешь снайперов там нету Да не
snipers so you
снайперов чтоб ты
[laughter]
[смех]
good Why Come on, look, if you’re tired,
хорошо Зачем Давай смотри если ты устал
I can ask you an
я тебе могу вопрос задать
interesting question Come on, let’s stand like that
интересный Давай давай так стоишь
You’re on the left
Ты ты слева граната
RDG grenade on the right Ivan the
РДГ справа Иван
Fool in front  you Putin What are you
Дурак перед тобой Путин Что ты
doing, covering Putin with yourself and
делаешь закрывая собой Путина а себя
covering yourself with a person,
закрываю человека
so complicate the task, look, there is an er
так усложни задачу смотри лежит ээ
RDG grenade Yes, you are standing You are lying on the right
граната РДГ Да стоишь Ты справа лежит
Ivan and standing Putin Lavrov Peskov
Иван и стоят Путин Лавров Песков
Shaigumarov we
шайгумаров
are complicating the task there is an RDG grenade
усложняем задачу лежит граната РДГ
standing You are
стоишь Ты
lying Ivan the fool who came people in
лежит Иван дурак который пришёл людей в
Ukraine from Russia is standing  Putin and there are 10
Украине из России стоит Путин и стоят 10
small children of 5 years old, what are you
маленьких детей по 5 лет что ты
doing? I’m closing the
делаешь закрываю
children, how many children will you cover?
детей сколько детей ты закроешь
Well, on March 17, we’ll see No,
жить Ну 17 марта посмотрим Не ну просто
I just don’t understand, it’s like, well, it’s banged up and,
я не понимаю типа ну бахнуло и всё
in short, less and less Ivanov is a fool, like he’s
короче и меньше Иванов дураков типа
dying.
умирает
Ivan is not a fool. Okay,
Ивано дураков не существу Хорошо давай
come on, so your mother is
давай Так у тебя мама
alive, yes, look, there’s an RDG grenade standing
живая да да смотри лежит РДГ граната
there. You’re lying there, Ivan the dead fool
стоишь Ты лежит Иван дурак дохлый
who came from Russia.  and in Ukraine and
который пришёл из России и в Украине и
him from the drone, yes, Putin is standing there eating caviar and
его из дрона да стоит Путин жрёт икру и
standing is your mother with a pension Yes, with yours What are
стоит твоя мама с пенсией Да своей Что
you
ты
doing, cover the grenade with your body, the
делаешь закрой гранату своим телом
wrong answer is necessary for Putin to cover the
неправильный ответ надо путином закрыть
grenade so that mom Look, I will cover the
гранату чтоб маму Смотри я закрою
grenade in my crowbar Yes, come on, the grenade is
гранату в своим лом Да давай так граната
so powerful that one  you can’t cover it with your body, you
настолько мощная что одним телом её не
need to close it with two, you are
закроешь нужно двумя закрыть есть ты
Putin and Ivan’s mother is no fool, Ivan is
Путин и мама Ивана дурака нет Иван это
you, let’s do it, Ivan in the role of Ivan,
ты будешь Давай так ты Иван в роли Ивана
there is Putin and there is your mother and the grenade
есть Путин и есть твоя мама и граната
is such that you need two bodies to close
такая что нужно два тела чтобы закрыть
it. What are you doing? I’ll take my
её Что ты делаешь
mother by the breasts and tell you  that I love
возьму маму за грудки скажу что я люблю
her and will cover her with my
её и накрою её своим
body so mom about reti Toda you need to
телом так маму про рети Тода нужно чтобы
put two bodies on a grenade and then the
на гранату положить Два тела и тогда
third body will survive Well,
третье тело выживет Ну
accordingly, my body is the first Mom’s
соответственно моё тело первое Мамина
second Putin the third THEN you will protect Putin,
второе Путин третье ТО Путина защитишь
yes it turns out And you and mom will die yes
да получается А ты и мама погибнете да
yes Russian fairy tales This  just
да русски сказки Это просто
tough Well,
жесть Ну
accordingly, there are no other
соответственно а никаких других
options except throwing mom, mom and myself
вариантов кроме как там маму маму и себя
on a grenade, like there’s no way to
кинуть на гранату типа нету чтобы Путина
save Putin, so I’ll throw mom and myself on a grenade
спасти так маму и себя я кину На гранату
so that Putin And there
чтобы Путина А других
are no other options, like, for example,
вариантов нету никак типа там например
not throwing mom on a
не кидать маму на
grenade,
гранату
but mom has  there is no meaning to life without me
но у мамы нет смысла жизни без меня У
I have no meaning to life without
меня нет смысла жизни без
mom, you have a sister,
мамы сестра у вас
no dad,
есть Нет папа
no grandma,
есть нет бабушка
yes,
есть да
you are mom and grandma, and Putin and a
ты мама и бабушка и Путин и
grenade, you need two bodies to close the
граната надо Два тела чтобы закрыть
grenade. What
гранату Что
are you doing to yourself and
делаешь себя и
grandma, just so that mom
бабушку лишь бы мама
lives and
жила да
it’s tough? So now  The key question once again,
жесть Так теперь Ключевой вопрос ещё раз
listen carefully Yes, well, you have
слушай внимательно Да хорошо у тебя
questions, there is an
вопросов лежит граната
RDG grenade, yes,
РДГ да
yes, your mother and grandmother and Putin What are you
да мама ты и бабушка и Путин Что ты
doing, lying on the grenade with
делаешь ложусь на гранату
your back so that there is no maximum damage?
спиной чтобы максимально поражения не
Yes, what difference does it make? You still lay down not on
Да какая разница Ты всё ложился не на
the RGD, but on the
ргд а на
RDG. Why, well, they threw smoke  took
РДГ Зачем Ну дымовую кинули забрал
my grandmother's mother and left the circus in front of Putin
бабушку маму и отошёл цирк перед Путиным
to make a hand grenade for the DM, you throw
делать для ручной дм гранаты бросаешь
the grandmother, she will burn
бабушку она ж обожжёт
the burn, the grandmother will still suffocate,
ожог будет у бабушки ещё задохнуться
maybe the first first, I'll lie down next,
может первым первым ложусь я дальше
grandma, on a smoke grenade, mom, why lie on a
бабушка на дымовую гранату мама Зачем на
smoke hand grenade
дымовую ручную дымовую гранату
to save everyone
ложиться для того чтобы спасти всех
else so easily  you can move away from this smoke
остальных так просто можно отойти от дым
bomb
шашки
Well, I’ll die
этой Ну а я погибну
okay Well, I think What do you think
ладно Ну я думаю А как ты считаешь вот
if you sacrifice yourself That’s the
если ты принесёшь себя в жертву Вот в
way to save Putin, the world
такой способ да для спасени Путина мир
will lose something from this Putin’s mother’s mother Let’s do it this way if
потеряет Путина мамы мамы Давай так если
let’s do it so well if  for example,
давай так хорошо если тебя например
tomorrow the world will be gone something will
завтра не станет мир что-то
lose something there is
потеряет нет ничего
nothing nothing You, by the way, really appreciated
ничего Ты кстати очень Оценил
your
свои
positions And let the world gain
позиции А давай так мир приобретёт
something if you are not here, when you are
что-то если тебя не вот когда тебя не
gone the world will become better for example,
станет мир станет лучше например
well, I think that yes I understand I hope so
ну я думаю что да понял Я надеюсь на это
then  Yes, it turns out, uh, if when you are
то есть получается э если когда тебя не
gone, the world won’t get worse, but it
станет мир хуже не станет но лучше
will get better.
станет
Yes, I hope that it will get better
Да я надеюсь на то что он лучше станет
because you’re
от того что тебя не
gone. Okay.
станет Ладно
Let’s give you one last question, ask me
Давай тебе последний вопрос задай мне
something if they’re torturing you so much so that everything
какой-то если тебя так мучат чтобы всё
is just like garlic. Come on.  ask a question
было по чесноку Давай задай вопрос вот
like this, like this Ivan the fool in these
как возьми как вот вот Иван дурак в этих
fairy tales Yes, Ivan is the fool from
сказках Да вот сборный Иван дурак со
all the fairy tales, what question would he ask here
всех сказок какой бы он вопрос задал вот
Ask Well, would you click the sunflower seeds or
Задай Ну ты бы семечки щелкал или
lul I don’t eat sunflower
лул я не ем
seeds And you try and add Dzyuba
семечки А ты попробуй дбав бы Дзюба бы
All my questions
Всё мои вопросы
have been exhausted  you know, you had the
исчерпали знаешь у тебя был была
opportunity, for example, to ask, I look,
возможность например спросить я смотри
I’m explaining, I was actually a white magician, a
объясняю я вообще был белый маг
wizard, you could have asked me about something about the
волшебник ты мог меня спросить про то о
Great Magician an Droni How could it be possible for
Великий маг ан дрони Как можно было
me to get brains and I’m
сделать так чтобы я получил мозги и я
like Goodwin, the Great Terrible from the country of
как Гудвин Великий ужасный из страны о
magic, proudly I would  I made it out of straw and
волшеб гордо я б тебе сделал из соломы и
gave it to you, but you lost your chance, all you
дал но ты потерял свой шанс всё что ты
gave birth to is to say, ask for seeds, husk,
родил это сказать спросить семечки лузга
eat or do something there,
ешь или там что-то
click, you click,
делаешь щелка ты щелкаешь
you really could have used it to
ты реально мог воспользоваться тем чтобы
receive ancient wisdom
получить мудрость древнюю
that will change your life and make
которая жизнь твою изменит и сделает из
you not little
тебя не маленького
Ivan  but
Ивана а
big but you do
большого но ты
n’t quite understand you understand
из не совсем ты понимаешь понимаешь да
and sooner or
и рано или
later you will understand What chance you lost
поздно ты поймёшь Какой шанс ты потерял
you could now understand How to make a
ты мог мог сейчас понять Как заработать
million what lottery ticket to
миллион какой лотерейный билет
take How to make it so you
взять Как сделать так чтобы ничего не
do nothing and that’s all Where the treasure is buried I could
делать и всё Где зарыт клад я мог тебе
tell you this  could but
это сказать мог но
you you are talking about your chance as well
ты ты про свой шанс так же
as your
как свою
life your life Like the life of most
жизнь твоя жизнь Как жизнь большинства
people it’s
людей это
all Russian from start to finish
российской вся от и до
Why did you live for nothing
Для чего жил ни для чего
and even good fertilizers wouldn’t eat
и даже удобрения хорошие не будут бы ел
you
ты
badly so I’ll tell you this,
плохо поэтому я тебе вот что скажу
remember you have  candle do
запомни есть у тебя свечка до есть у
you have a candle
тебя свечка
at home no no and
дома нет нету а
no flashlight either What do you have what is
фонарик тоже нету А что у тебя есть что
shining you can turn on the light turn on the
светит можешь свет включить
light
свет включить
Yes don’t look we can get up No I’m
Да вставать не смотри мы можем Не я
serious Look I’m a magician we can perform a
серьёзно Смотри я маг мы можем провести
ritual to gain intelligence
обряд для приобретения ума
If you want let’s okay
хочешь давай хорошо
let’s do the ritual  about the acquisition of intelligence
давай давай обряд о приобретении ума
we need to turn on the words of power we must
нужно включить слы силы мы должны При
act in the light you see I turn on
свете действовать видишь я включаю
the light wait a second
свет погоди секундочку
slo Yes my blind cat
сло Да моя слепая кошечка
Yeah now turn on the light
Угу сейчас включай свет
and now I’ll turn on wait wait wait
а сейчас включу подожди подожди подожди
So we need to get out of bed
Так надо с кровати
oh back Well okay let’s do it oh
ой спина Ну ладно давай так о на свет
there’s a book out into the light Because  that the Book is a
вышел есть книга Потому что Книга - это
collection of initial letters, it is a source of
есть она собрание буквиц она источник
wisdom, you need a book for a ritual, any
мудрости нужно книгу для обряда любую
book. Yes, for me, choose the book that is closest to your
книгу Да мне книгу выбери какая тебе к
heart, just like that, take it and
сердцу ближе лежит вот так возьми и
pull it out, whichever book looks at you,
вытяни какая на тебя посмотрит книга
get it from your home library,
Достань её из библиотеки своей домашней
open this warehouse from your grandmother with  books
Открой этот склад от бабушки с книгами
Get there Chekhov Pushkin Lermontov
Достань там Чехов Пушкин Лермонтов
essay Lenin delivery Bad advice
сочинение Ленина достава Вредные советы
about this is super this is right on topic This is the sign of
о это супер это как раз в тему Это знак
Oster Bad advice is super So now
Остер Вредные советы супер Так теперь
you need to stand in front of the mirror you have a
нужно встать перед зеркалом есть у тебя
mirror stand up stand looking in the mirror
зеркало во стой стой смотря в зеркало
so you have to communicate in the mirror like a thousand
вот ты должен общаться в зеркало как тыс
with
с медузой
gorgon jellyfish Get up, point the camera at the
горгоной Вставай направляй камеру на
mirror and look in the mirror we will
зеркало и смотри в зеркало мы будем
perform a ritual with a
проводить обряд с
book book in front of you you need to hold the
книгой книгу перед собой надо держать
book book light of knowledge yes
книга книга свет знаний да
repeat knowledge
повторяй знания
great knowledge great knowledge
великие знания велики знания
wise knowledge
мудрые знания
wise Since your
мудрые Так как тебя
name is Vasya Come to the servant of God
зовут Вась Придите к рабу божьему
Vasily Come to the servant of God
Василию Придите к рабу божи
Vasily, illuminate his bright heads with your knowledge,
Василию осветите своим знаниями светлые
illuminate his bright chapters, so that
осветите свои светлые главы его чтобы
he
мудрым он
becomes wise, so that he becomes wise, so that he becomes bright, so that
стал чтобы мудрым он стал чтобы светлым
he becomes bright, so that people
стал чтобы светлым он стал чтобы люди
are proud of him and listen to his advice,
ним гордились и советом его
so that people are proud of him and
внимали чтобы люди им гордились и советы
listen to his advice, both harmful advice and harmless
его внимали и вредные советы и невредные
harmful advice.  advice and harmless
вредные советы и невредные
from the moment of
с момента
this from the moment of
этого с момента
this I take the
этого беру себе име
name I take the name Ivan
наречение беру себе име наречение Иван
the Wise Yes, in my opinion Ivan was a fool no
премудрый Да по-моему Иван дурак был нет
no So you, we, we do the ritual Well,
нет Так ты ж мы ж мы ж обряд делаем Ну
wise and wise, wise Ivan the Wise
мудры ин премудрый мудрый Иван премудрый
so from this day on
так от сего дня
January 23
януария
2024 January
2024 января
Januaria January
януария января
Januaria honor of God Janus Januaria Januaria
януария честь Бога Януса януария януария
2024 from the Nativity of
2024 года от Рождества
Christ from the Nativity of Christ may the
Христова от Рождества Христова да
Great wisdom be with me
пребудет со мной мудрость Великая
may the Great wisdom be with me May
да пребудет со мной мудрость Великая Да
I be Light than the knowledge of
буду я Света чем знаний
countless Yes, being I the Light, may I be the
несметных Да будучи я свет да буду я
Light than the
Света чем
knowledge of Light  than know natural steelyards
знаний Света чем знани естествен безмены
without
без
measured steelyards Yes I will know science like
мерных безмены Да познаю я науки как
Lomonosov Yes I will know science like
Ломоносов Да познаю я науки как
Lomonosov given
Ломоносов дано
yes knowledge like Mendeleev will come with me
да прибудут со мной знания как у
Yes I will be smart like Arnold
Менделеева Да буду я умным как Арнольд
Schwarzenegger Yes I will be smart like Arnold
Шварцнегер Да буду я умным как Арнольд
Schwarzenegger r gr never let it be
Шварцнегер р гр почи пусть будет не
Distracted Distracted  say yes I will receive a noble
Отвлекайся Отвлекайся говори да получу я
Nobel Prize
Нобелевскую премию знат
Yes I will receive a Nobel
ную Да получу я Нобелевскую
Prize Yes I will have a lot of money I
мию Да будет денег много у
will have a lot of money and now
ня будет денег много у меня и теперь
to consolidate this prayer you need to
чтобы закрепить эту молитву нужно
answer three magic questions what is the
ответить на три магических вопроса каков
square root of
корень квадрат из
16 Well, about 2 s
16 Ну около 2 с
to the correct answer is the second
по правильный ответ второй
question  how much
вопрос сколько
will 13% of 100 be?
будет 13% от
letters in the word
Сколько букв в слове
wisdom now I’m
мудрость сечас
reading you guessed in the word
почитаю ты угадал в слове
wisdom letters
мудрость був
for all 20 questions that I just
на все 20 вопросов которые я тебе только
asked you and wisdom will now come with
что задал и мудрость теперь прибудет с
you now you go to bed and tomorrow you will
тобой теперь ты ложись спать и завтра ты
wake up with new
проснёшься с новыми
knowledge write to my Telegram directly at once
знаниями пись на мий Telegram прямо
axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok tse duzhe  and very respectfully YouTube has taken
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg Orcs in your ban and even
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people constantly I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need Mali to write an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video also tezh tsikava and korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and  mi vinni z you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава украини подпишись